That it has happened, hey
come doctor sahib, you have
not changed anything by going to the city, so tell me
in the last one year how many people have come to your village from far away city for
treatment, because the
village health center has also changed, it has become
better than before, deliveries have taken place from children to
old people, and what's more, there is
arrangement for blood test, online treatment,
only one thing is missing, that is yours, it is
fine, I will also stay, it is a promise, a
sure promise
[praise]
that such a promise has been fulfilled by ICICI
Lombard policy where in Haldi, it is taking care of the safety of the citizens by fulfilling the needs of the
health centers of many villages of its initial